<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ChineseMobile</string>
    <string name="new_user_sign_up">New User? <b><u>Sign Up</u></b></string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string><!--make SignUp bold-->
    <string name="to_char">To Chinese Character</string><!--make SignUp bold-->
    <string name="intro01">Chinese is spreading globally and Mandarin speakers are increasing worldwide. Learning Mandarin Chinese has brought attention to the people around the world.</string>
    <string name="intro02">The Chinese language is a logographic language system, unlike English, which uses an alphabetic system.</string>
    <string name="intro03">There are two written forms in the Mandarin Chinese language: Chinese characters and Hanyu Pinyin.</string>
    <string name="intro04">There are two types of Chinese character writing systems in the Chinese language, namely Traditional Chinese and Simplified Chinese.</string>
    <string name="char01">Strokes are the basic components in Chinese Characters writing. Chinese radicals and characters are formed with different
        combinations of strokes ranging from one to more strokes.</string>
    <string name="char02">The combination of different characters will become a new word and give a different meaning. Many Mandarin characters are generally written in
        either component or compound characters.</string>
    <string name="char03">For example, 女(woman) and 子(child) are component characters that are used to form other compound characters, 好(good). </string>
    <string name="pinyin01">Each Chinese character has a transcribe of English alphabets known as Hanyu Pinyin or Pinyin. For example, 马 (character) has a Pinyin form of “mǎ”. </string>
    <string name="pinyin02">Besides, each syllable and character have four different tones that carry one or more meaning. For example, 妈 (mother), 麻(hemp), 马(horse), 骂(to scold) are all pronounced with Pinyin “ma” but with different tones</string>


</resources>